calverteducation.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Calvert Education

**CALVERT EDUCATION PRIVACY NOTICE**  
Calvert Education Services, LLC (Calvert Education) has established this privacy policy to let you know how we collect, use, share and protect information that we may gather from this website. This policy does not apply to information that we may collect from you outside of this website (e.g. over the phone, by fax, through paper applications, at events or through other means). Furthermore, it does not apply to “educational records” as that term is defined in the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act, 20 U.S.C. § 1232g and the implementing regulations thereof (“FERPA”). Calvert Education covenants at all times to comply with FERPA and no provision in this policy is intended nor authorizes Calvert Education to violate FERPA, or any other law applicable to you or your personal information. If there is any conflict between this policy and FERPA or other applicable law, the obligations under FERPA or the other applicable law control.

Calvert Education reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, if we make merely ministerial, immaterial or non-substantive changes, we will simply post them on the website. If we make any material changes to this policy, we will post any revised Privacy Policy on the website and provide a notice for a reasonable period of time after such change that identifies such changes, and if Calvert Education has your email address, will email you that such policy has changed. You must enable your email program to accept our email and we are not responsible for filters, spam blocks or other devices, software or other components or causes outside of our control that may prevent you from receiving our emails. The most current version of this policy is always available by clicking on the “Privacy Policy” link located at the bottom of the website’s home page.

Your use of this website constitutes acceptance of this Privacy Policy and we do not consent to your use of this website unless you agree to this Privacy Policy, therefore, if you do not agree to the provisions of this Privacy Policy or any revised policy, please exit this website immediately and do not use this website. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy they shall become effective retroactively, unless you notify us in writing that you do not agree to such changes within the earlier of 30 calendar days of the date we changed such terms or 5 calendar days after you first became aware of such changes.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
In this Privacy Policy, _“personally identifiable information”_ means information that identifies you, such as your name, address, email, date of birth, age, physical attributes and similar types of information. Except for your personally identifiable information, Calvert Education is the sole owner of all information collected on the website. With respect to your personally identifiable information, you grant us a worldwide, royalty-free, license and right to:

– make use thereof to operate the website and provide services to you;

– to comply with applicable law, which may include, for example, responding to governmental requests for your information, and responding to court orders and subpoenas by providing responsive information which may include your personally identifiable information;

– if you opt into such use, to provide your information to third parties that may be interested in providing services to you;

– to retain if we determine in good faith that applicable law requires us to retain such information (however, our retention of such information is solely for the benefit, we owe no duty to, and are not responsible for, any loss or destruction of your personally identifiable information);

– to our third party contractors that we have selected to assist us in providing the services offered in the website; and

– if we re-organize, engage in a merger, acquisition, sale of substantially all of our assets, or engage in other similar types of transactions in which our business is sold or ownership thereof is changed, you agree and consent to the transfer of your personally identifiable information to such successor, assign or another third party, provided that they agree and shall continue to perform this Privacy Policy.

We only have access to/collect personally identifiable information about you that you voluntarily give us. Other information we collect automatically – such information is not personally identifiable information; it relates to your use of the website and other statistical and page view information that our software collects automatically and is not linked to your personally identifiable information.

When you register your children for enrollment in Calvert Education schools or schools of our affiliated companies, we and they may collect information regarding you and your children; this information is only used to provide you with information about special promotions, new products, and services, or upcoming events from Calvert Education and its affiliated schools, and only in compliance with FERPA.

We understand that our student users who are under 13 year of age need special safeguards and privacy protection, and it is our intent to fully comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We do not collect personal information from children online at any point. Calvert Education only receives personal information about your children directly from you when you enroll your children into schools which we administer, and that information is used in compliance with FERPA.

We cannot prohibit minors from visiting this website. We must rely on parents, guardians and those responsible for supervising children under 13 to decide which materials are appropriate for such children to view and/or purchase. Pursuant to 47 U.S.C. Section 230 (d), as amended, we hereby notify you that parental control protections (such as computer hardware, software or filtering services) are commercially available that may assist you in limiting access to material that is harmful to minors.

**Security for Personally Identifiable Information**  
We take the security of personally identifiable information very seriously. Our website and database servers are hosted in a secured physical and network environment. Reasonable efforts are made to secure web servers, networks, host operating systems and databases against unauthorized access. Please remember that the security measures taken above are not foolproof; no website can guarantee that personally identifiable information will be protected in all situations. Therefore we can only state that we will make a reasonable effort to protect from unauthorized access the information that you provide, and that if we are notified of a breach, we will comply with applicable law, however, unless a statute provides you a right that cannot be waived, you specifically waive and covenant not to sue us for any data loss or breach of our system resulting in loss of personal information.

**Social Networks and Other Online Services**  
Calvert Education may offer links to or integration with online social media networks and tools (e.g. Facebook, YouTube, Twitter, etc. ) to you, the parent(s), on our websites. We are not responsible for the data collection, information use and sharing, and other policies or procedures of third party websites or services that we link to or integrate with. Please be aware that in some cases, and depending on how you have configured your privacy settings in such services, anyone may be able to read messages you post on social media websites and therefore your information that is linked in with or made available to these sites or services may no longer be private. We cannot guarantee the security of such information that you disclose or communicate online in public areas, and you do so at your own risk.

In some cases, we may permit you to integrate postings you have made on third-party sites including social networks, on our site. In such cases, we reserve the right to monitor the content that we allow you to integrate with our social media website and to delete, obscure or otherwise make unavailable your postings if we deem it necessary to do so.

**Links**  
This website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of any other website that collects personally identifiable information.

**Electronic communications**  
You agree to transact business with Us using electronic communications, either via web forms on the website or via email. Electronic communications will be deemed received by you when your email system reports that any email we send you, has been received by your system, regardless of whether you ever actually open or read such email. We may, but are not required, to use return receipt requests. Unless specifically required by applicable law, you consent to receive all notices, information, and other communications from Us concerning any subject matter, via electronic email. It is your responsibility to maintain a valid email address, and we may terminate your access to the website at any time that we determine you are in violation of these terms of use or failure to maintain a valid email address.

**Opt Out**  
You May request to opt out of future marketing communications from Calvert Education by making a request in writing to [unsubscribe@calvertservices.org](mailto:unsubscribe@calvertservices.org). Allow up to 30 days to be fully suppressed from our marketing lists.

Calvert Education Services  
215 Schilling Circle, Suite 106  
Hunt Valley, MD 21031

_Last Updated February 22, 2016_
